<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Seth Feldman – Advancing Cybersecurity Through Strategy, Detection, and Leadership</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Seth Feldman – Advancing Cybersecurity Through Strategy, Detection, and Leadership</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Building resilient security teams in today&#39;s threat landscape</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/building-security-teams/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/building-security-teams/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;building-resilient-security-teams-in-todays-threat-landscape&#34;&gt;Building resilient security teams in today&amp;rsquo;s threat landscape&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Fifteen years of leading security teams across startups and enterprises has taught me one truth: exceptional security doesn&amp;rsquo;t come from the latest tools or biggest budgets. It comes from people who can think critically, adapt quickly, and translate complex risks into business language.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The landscape has shifted dramatically since I started building teams. Today&amp;rsquo;s security leaders face a perfect storm of challenges—3.5 million unfilled cybersecurity positions globally, budget constraints replacing talent scarcity as the primary hiring barrier, and AI fundamentally changing how we approach threat detection and response.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cloud Security in 2024: Hard-Won Lessons from the Trenches</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/cloud-security-lessons-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/cloud-security-lessons-2024/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;cloud-security-in-2024-hard-won-lessons-from-the-trenches&#34;&gt;Cloud Security in 2024: Hard-Won Lessons from the Trenches&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Five years ago, cloud security felt like the Wild West. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s a mature discipline with established patterns, but the stakes have never been higher. After securing cloud environments across healthcare, finance, and technology companies, here are the lessons that separate successful cloud security programs from expensive failures.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-shared-responsibility-reality-check&#34;&gt;The Shared Responsibility Reality Check&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;what-cloud-providers-actually-secure&#34;&gt;What Cloud Providers Actually Secure&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Cloud providers secure the infrastructure, not your data or applications. This sounds obvious, but I&amp;rsquo;ve seen countless organizations assume their cloud provider handles security &amp;ldquo;end-to-end.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero Trust Architecture: A Practical Implementation Guide</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/zero-trust-implementation-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/zero-trust-implementation-guide/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;zero-trust-architecture-a-practical-implementation-guide&#34;&gt;Zero Trust Architecture: A Practical Implementation Guide&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;After implementing Zero Trust architectures across multiple organizations over the past five years, I&amp;rsquo;ve learned that success depends more on practical execution than perfect theory. This guide shares the real-world lessons that make the difference between a successful Zero Trust transformation and an expensive security theater exercise.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-zero-trust-really-means&#34;&gt;What Zero Trust Really Means&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Zero Trust isn&amp;rsquo;t a product you can buy or a checklist you can complete. It&amp;rsquo;s a security philosophy that assumes no user, device, or network location is inherently trustworthy. Every access request must be verified, authorized, and continuously monitored.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/resume/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;professional-summary&#34;&gt;Professional Summary&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Accomplished and innovative cybersecurity professional with over 20 years of extensive experience in the Information Security sector, specializing in custom threat detection, security engineering, endpoint, and network security. Proven expertise in understanding penetration testing procedures to identify vulnerabilities and recommend robust security solutions. Solid track record of developing and implementing comprehensive security protocols, with a strong ability to identify, evaluate, and mitigate potential risks and threats. Adept at leading cross-functional teams and managing multiple projects concurrently. A dynamic leader that consistently stays at the forefront of emerging trends, technologies, and advancements in cybersecurity. Passionately committed to ensuring the integrity, confidentiality, and availability of corporate data and information systems.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
